Records of the Education Sector
World Bank Group Archives
- Staff and consultant reports and documents, 1967, 1974 - 1990; WB IBRD/IDA WB_IBRD/IDA_88-11; 22.68 linear feet of textual records
  - Primary Education in Western Africa by B. Fredriksen - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01253675
  - The World Educational Crisis Revisited by P.H. Coombs - 1v, 1983-12-01 - ?; 01253676
  - The Payoff to Better Schooling: A Case Study of Tunisian Secondary Schools by M. Carnoy, R. Sack and H. Thias - 1v, 01253678
  - Implementing Innovative Projects: A Critical Review of the Literature by P. Hurst - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01253679
  - Cognitive Skills: Their Determinants and Influence on Earnings in Two Poor Urban Economics by R. Sabot, A. Berry, A. Hazlewood and J. Knight - 1v, 1981-02-01 - ?; 01253680
  - Does the Expansion of Education Compress the Structure of Wages and Reduce the Inequality of Pay? A Preliminary Analysis by Sabot, Berry, Hazlewood and Knight - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01253682
  - Bibliography of World Bank Research on the Quality of Education in Developing Countries by Heyneman - 1v, 1976-01-01 - ?; 01253683
  - Forecasting Manpower Demand by M. Zymelman - 1v, 1980-07-01 - ?; 01253684
  - Determinants of Sixth Grade Student Achievement in Peru by A.M. Arriagada - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253685
  - Information Needs in Educational Planning by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1980-01-01 - ?; 01253686
  - Education Sector Support Strategy Paper by M. Hultin - 1v, 1980-09-01 - ?; 01253687
  - Seminar on School Media Services: A Perspective from Developing Countries by F. A. Ogunsheye - 1v, 1982-04-01 - ?; 01253713
  - The Teacher-Learning Role of Media Centers/Libraries (Background Paper) by M. H. Mahar - 1v, 1982-01-01 - ?; 01253717
  - The Organization, Structure, Staffing, and Administration of School Library Media Centers (Background Paper) by G. G. Hodges - 1v, 1982-10-19 - ?; 01253714
  - Training for Public Administration and Management in Developing Countries: A Review (Background Paper) by S. Paul - 1v, 01253720
  - African Regional Seminar on Education Evaluation (IIEP/IBRD), 1974-09-30 - 1975-05-02; 01253724
  - Schooling for Development? Students and Workers in Tunisia by J. Simmons and S. Erkut - 1v, 1975-12-01 - ?; 01253722
  - Education and Development: Views from the World Bank by A. Habte, G. Psacharopoulos, and S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253723
  - Issues in Non-Formal Education and Training for Rural Development by C.W. Gilpin - 1v, 1979-07-01 - ?; 01253727
  - Educational Issues in Pakistan: A Sector Memorandum J. Simmons and P. Brock - 1v, 1977-08-01 - ?; 01253725
  - Political Economy of Education for Village Development by J. Simmons - 1v, 1978-10-01 - ?; 01253726
  - Universal Primary Education: An African Dilemma by K. H. Lee - 1v, 1984-03-01 - ?; 01253731
  - Education and Private Versus Public Sector Pay by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1983-06-01 - ?; 01253841
  - An Analysis of the Determinants of the demand for Upper Secondary Education in Portugal by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1982-01-01 - ?; 01253842
  - Student Expectations and Graduate Market Performance in Egypt by G. Psacharopoulos and B. Sanyal - 1v, 1982-01-01 - ?; 01253843
  - Expanding Education through User Charges: What can be Achieved in Malawi and other LDCs? by A. Mingar and J. P. Tan - 1v, 1985-08-01 - ?; 01253736
  - Educational Research Capabilities in Third World Countries by T. Husen - 1v, 01253742
  - The Willingness to Pay for Public Secondary Education: Evidence from Tanzania by J. P. Tan - 1v, 1983-08-01 - ?; 01253739
  - Measuring the Economy Efficiency of Project Related Training: Some Evidence from Agricultural Projects by A. Mingat - 1v, 1984-04-19 - ?; 01253751
  - Income Distribution, Education and Capital Accumulation by A. K. Dasgupta - 1v, 1979-03-01 - ?; 01253745
  - Who Profits from the Public Funding of Education? A Comparison by World Regions by A. Mingat and J. P. Tan - 1v, 1984-11-05 - ?; 01253748
  - Private Enrollments and Expenditure on Education: Some Macro Trends by J. P. Tan - 1v, 1984-10-17 - ?; 01253749
  - Recovering the Cost of Public Higher Education in LDCs: To What Extent are Loan Schemes an Efficient Instrument? by A. Mingat, J. P. Tan, and M. Hoque - 1v, 1984-08-03 - ?; 01253750
  - The Contribution of Education to Economic Growth: International Comparisons by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253752
  - Education Costs and Financing in Africa: Some Facts and Possible Lines of Action by A. Mingat and G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1985-10-25 - ?; 01253753
  - A Cost-Benefit Approach to Educational Planning in Developing Countries by M. Blaug - 1v, 1967-12-20 - ?; 01253755
  - African Regional Seminar on Educational Evaluation - 1v, 1975-04-07 - 1975-05-02; 01253754
  - The Economics of Being Poor by T. W. Schultz (Nobel Lecture) - 1v, 1979-12-10 - ?; 01253756
  - Education and development: From the Age of Innocence to the Age of Skepticism by H. N. Weiler (Stanford University) - 1v, 1977-12-01 - ?; 01253757
  - Educational Management: System Development and System Maintenance by G. Neave - 1v, 1985-02-01 - ?; 01253758
  - The Exess Demand for Education in Developing Countries by G. Lassibille (not Approved) - 1v, 01253764
  - Financing Public Higher Education in Developing Countries: The Potential Role of Loan Schemes by A. Mingat and J. P. Tan (not Approved) - 1v, 1986-02-01 - ?; 01253765
  - Is Primary School Quality Eroding in the Third World? by B. Fuller (not Approved) - 1v, 1986-01-01 - ?; 01253766
  - The Search for School Effects in Developing Countries: 1966 - 1986 by S. Heyneman (not Approved) - 1v, 1986-02-01 - ?; 01253767
  - A Review of Educational Research Capabilities in Third World Countries by T. Husen (not Approved) - 1v, 01253768
  - Taxonomies of Skill Development: A Search for Criteria to Predict the Relative Efficiency of Alternative Programs of Occupational training by C. S. Benson - 1v, 1987-02-25 - ?; 01253769
  - Education and Training Programs and Projects for Urban Poor by H. M. Phillips - 1v, 1978-01-01 - ?; 01253770
  - Higher Education Research and development by J. P. Powell - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01253774
  - Financing Public Higher Education in Developing Countries by A. Mingat and J. p. Tann - 1v, 1986-01-01 - ?; 01253775
  - Childhood Malnutrition and Schooling in the Terai Region of Nepal by P. R. Moock and J. Leslie - 1v, 1984-05-01 - ?; 01253776
  - Expanding Education through User Charges in LDCs: What can be Achieved? by A. Mingat and J. P. Tan - 1v, 1985-02-01 - ?; 01253777
  - Examinations Reform: The Kenya Experience by H.C.A. Somerset - 1v, 1983-07-01 - ?; 01253778
  - Education as an Investment by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1982-09-01 - ?; 01253779
  - The Internal Efficiency of Higher Education in Developing Countries by A. Gorham and R. Ko-chih Tung - 1v, 1982-04-25 - ?; 01253783
  - The Planning of Education: Where do we Stand? by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1986-11-01 - ?; 01253781
  - Education for National Development: World Bank Activities by A. Habte and S. Heyneman - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253792
  - Educational Costing and Financing in Developing Countries, with Special Reference to Sub-Saharan Africa by J. C. Eicher - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253788
  - Efficiency and Equity Implications of Subsidies of Secondary Education in Kenya by J. Armitage and R. H. Sabot - 1v, 1984-04-01 - ?; 01253790
  - World Bank: Role in Educational Development by A. Habte - 1v, 1985-01-01 - ?; 01253808
  - Economic Development and Cultural Change Why Males Earn more: Location and Training of Brazilian School Teachers by N. Birdsall and M. L. Fox - 1v, 1985-04-01 - ?; 01253812
  - Does Geographical Aggregation Cause Overestimates of the Returns to Schooling? by N. Birdsall and J. R. Behrman - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01253813
  - Research in Population Economics: A Cost of Siblings: Child Schooling in Urban Colombia by N. Birdsall - 1v, 1980-01-01 - ?; 01253814
  - Journal of Development Economics: Public Inputs and Child Schooling in Brazil by N. Birdsall - 1v, 1983-10-01 - ?; 01253824
  - Economics of Education Review: ChildRen's Education and the Intergenerational Transmission of Inequality: A Simulation by N. Birdsall and O. A. Meesook - 1v, 1986-01-01 - ?; 01253825
  - Revista Colombiana de Educacion by E. V. Bustillo and P. L. Trouchon - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253826
  - American Economic Review: The Quality of Schooling: Quality Alone is Misleading by J. R. Behrman and N. Birdsall - 1v, 1983-12-01 - ?; 01253827
  - American Economic Review: The Equity-Productivity Tradeoff: Public School Resources in Brazil by J. R. Behrman and N. Birdsall - 1v, 1985-11-01 - ?; 01253828
  - Demand for Primary Schooling in Rural Mali: Should User Fees be Increased? by N. Birdsall - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253829
  - Health Policy and Education: Parental Education and Child Health: Intracountry Evidence by S. H. Cochrane, J. Leslie, and D. J. O'Hara - 1v, 1982-01-01 - ?; 01253830
  - Research on Effective Schools Implications for Less-Developed Countries, Developed Countries by E. Cohn and R. A. Rossmiller - 1v, 1985-07-02 - ?; 01253831
  - Educational Reform in India: A Century of Effort by P. R. Panchamukhi - 1v, 1978-11-01 - ?; 01253833
  - Educational Reform in the U.S.: An Historical and Statistical Survey by H. Gintis, S. Bowles - 1v, 1979-06-01 - ?; 01253835
  - The Economicss of Early Childhood Education and Day-Care by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1982-01-01 - ?; 01253837
  - Welfare Effects of Government Intervention in Education by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1986-07-01 - ?; 01253838
  - The Effect of Diversified Schools on Employment Status and Earnings in Colombia by G. Psacharopoulos and A. Zabalza - 1v, 1984-06-01 - ?; 01253840
  - Educational Planning: A Reappraisal by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1978-01-01 - ?; 01253845
  - The Perverse Effects of Public Subsidization of Education or How Equitable is Free Education? by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1977-01-01 - ?; 01253846
  - Returns to Education: An International Update and Implications by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1985-01-01 - ?; 01253848
  - Forecasting Manpower Demand by M. Zymelman - 1v, 1980-07-01 - ?; 01253849
  - Vocational Industrial Training in Developing Countries by M. Zymelman - 1v, 1978-11-06 - ?; 01253850
  - The Burden of Educational Expenditures and its Forecast by M. Zymelman - 1v, 1978-01-04 - ?; 01253852
  - Education, Employment and Inequality in LDCs by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01253854
  - Education and Structure of Earnings in Portugal by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01253855
  - Overview of the World Bank's Research on Education by P. R. Moock and R. S. Horn - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253856
  - Education and Technical Efficiency in Small-Farm Production by P. R. Moock - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01253857
  - Characteristics and Determinants of Child Nutritional Status in Nepal by R. Martorell, J. Leslie, and P. Moock - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01253976
  - China/World Bank: University Development by A. H. Ter Weele - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01253992
  - Further Evidence on Economics of Scale in Higher Education by K. H. Lee - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01253998
  - The International Flow of Third Level Lesser Developed Country Students to Developed Countries: Determinants and Implications by K. H. Lee and J. P. Tan - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01254003
  - Equity and an Alternative Educational Method: A Korean Case Study by K. W. Lee - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01254005
  - Dilemmas of Diversification: Problems Associated with Vocational Education in Developing Countries by K. Lillis and D. Hogan - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01254008
  - Labor Force Experience and Earnings: Women with Children by V. Levine and P. Moock - 1v, 1982-04-01 - ?; 01254007
  - Language Policies for African Primary Education by D. L. Macmillan - 1v, 1980-07-01 - ?; 01254010
  - Financing Education in Sub-Saharan Africa by A. Mingat and G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1985-03-01 - ?; 01254013
  - Subsidization of Higher Education Versus Expansion of Primary Enrollments: What can a Shift of Resources Achieve in Sub-Saharan Africa? by A. Mingat and J. P. Tan - 1v, 1984-06-01 - ?; 01254018
  - The Private Direct Cost of Secondary Schooling in Tanzania by J. P. Tan - 1v, 1984-03-01 - ?; 01254019
  - External Advisory Panel Report - 1v, 1978-10-31 - ?; 01254024
  - Local Initiatives and their Implications for a Multilevel Approach to School Improvement in Thailand by M. C. Tsang and C. W. Wheeler - 1v, 1989-09-01 - ?; 01254124
  - Universities and Development: The Evolving Role of the World Bank by A. Ziderman - 1v, 1989-12-01 - ?; 01254125
  - Quality of Education and Economic Growth by L. C. Solmon - 1v, 01254021
  - Education and Occupational Attainment in Chile: The Effects of Educational Quality, Attainment, and Achievement by E. Schiefelbein and J. P. Farrell - 1v, 1984-02-01 - ?; 01254022
  - On Equity in Education Again - An International Comparison - Education and Training Department - Journal of Human Resources - September 13, 1984 - Alain Mingat and Jee-Peng Tan, 1984-09-13; 01255701
  - A Note on Preschool-Age Investment in Human Capital in Developing Countries by M. Selowsky - 1v, 1976-07-01 - ?; 01254023
  - Retention of Cognitive Skills Acquired in Primary School by J. Simmons - 1v, 1976-01-01 - ?; 01254035
  - The Determinants of Earnings: Towards an Improved Model by J. Simmons - 1v, 1974-03-01 - ?; 01254037
  - Public Inputs and Child Schooling in Brazil by N. Birdall - 1v, 1982-03-01 - ?; 01254039
  - The Quality of Schooling: Quantity Alone is Misleading by J. R. Behrman and N. Birdsall - 1v, 1983-12-01 - ?; 01254040
  - The Determinants of School Achievement in Developing Countries: A Review of the Research by J. Simmons - 1v, 1975-01-01 - ?; 01254036
  - World Bank Lending in Education: One View of how it happens by L. Wolff - 1v, 01254038
  - A User's Guide to the Educational Planning Models by M. Bartlett and P. Roizen - 1v, 1977-03-01 - ?; 01254042
  - The Quality of Education and Economic Development by S. P. Heyneman and D. S. White - 1v, 1986-01-01 - ?; 01254043
  - Diversifying Secondary School Curricula in Developing Countries: An Implementation History and some Policy Options, Research on Education in Developing Countries by S. Heyneman - 2, 1983-01-01 - 1985-12-31; 01254045
  - Evaluation of the Philippines Textbook Project: Multivariate Analysis of Data from Grades 1 and 2 by D. T. Jamison and X. Montenegro - 1v, 1980-05-01 - ?; 01254044
  - Human Resources in Africa: A Continent in Rapid Change by M. J. Bowman, R. H. Sabot - 1v, 1982-08-02 - 1982-08-12; 01254046
  - Lifetime Profiles of Earnings and Employment: A Survey by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 01254049
  - Education Sector Support Strategy Paper by Mats Hultin - 1v, 1980-09-01 - ?; 01254047
  - Comparative Education Review by A. Mingat and J. P. Tan - 1v, 1986-05-01 - ?; 01254048
  - Determinants of Sixth Grade Student Achievement in Peru by A. M. Arriagata - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01254051
  - The Internal Efficiency of Higher Education in Developing Countries by A. Gorham and K. C. Tung - 1v, 1982-04-25 - ?; 01254052
  - Assessing Training Priorities in Developing Countries: Current Practice and Possible Alternatives by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1984-06-01 - ?; 01254058
  - The Contribution of Education to Economic Growth: International Comparisons by G. Psacharopoulos with Comments by T. W. Shultz - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01254062
  - World Bank Research News: Educational Research at the World Bank by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01254063
  - Economic of Education Review: The Effect of Diversified Schools on Employment Status and Earnings in Colombia by G. Psacharopoulos and A. Zabalza - 1v, 1984-01-01 - ?; 01254064
  - Financing Education in Developing Countries by G. Psacharopoulos, J. P. Tan, and E. Jimenez - 1v, 1986-07-01 - ?; 01254111
  - Education and Occupational Attainment in Chile: The Effects of Educational Quality, Attainment, and Achievement by E. Schiefelbein and J. P. Farrel - 1v, 1984-02-01 - ?; 01254112
  - Nutrition, Health, and Education: The Economic Significance of Complementarities at Early Age by M. Selowsky - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01254113
  - Why Impoverished Children Do Well in Ugandan Schools by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1979-01-01 - ?; 01254115
  - Education During a Period of Austerity: Uganda, 1971-1981 by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01254116
  - Skills Training for Productivity: Strategies for Improved Efficiency in Developing Countries by J. Middleton, A. Ziderman, and A. V. Adams - 1v, 1990-01-01 - ?; 01254129
  - Reappraisal of Educational Planning by J. Tinberger and G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01254114
  - The Distribution of Primary School Quality within High-Low Income Countries by S. P. Heyneman and W. A. Loxley - 1v, 1983-02-01 - ?; 01254120
  - The Two Elements of School Mapping: School Place Location Planning and School Resource Location Planning by S. Heyneman and W. Gould - 1v, 1978-09-01 - ?; 01254117
  - Influences on Academic Achievement Across High and Low Income Countries: A Re-Analysis of IEA Data by S. P. Heyneman and W. A. Loxley - 1v, 1982-01-01 - ?; 01254118
  - Participation in Schooling: Determinants and Learning Outcomes in Nepal by D. T. Jamison and M. E. Lockheed - 1v, 1984-06-01 - ?; 01254122
  - The Effect of Primary-School Quality on Academic Achievement across Twenty-nine High-and Low-Income Countries by S. P. Heyneman and W. A. Loxley - 1v, 1983-05-01 - ?; 01254123
  - The Role of Educational Certification in Raising Earnings: Evidence from Israeli Census Data by A. Ziderman - 1v, 1990-01-01 - ?; 01254132
  - Vocational and Technical Education in Peru by R. Bellow and P. Moock - 1v, 1990-04-01 - ?; 01254133
  - Vocational Schooling, Occupational Matching and Labor Market Earnings in Israel by S. Neuman and A. Ziderman - 1v, 1990-03-01 - ?; 01254134
  - Building Technological Capability in Developing Countries and the Role of the World Bank by C. Dahlman - 1v, 1990-01-08 - ?; 01254155
  - How can Schooling Help Improve the Lives of the Poorest? The Need for Radical Reform by N. Bennet - 1v, 1989-09-01 - ?; 01254162
  - Education for All in Low Income and Adjusting Countries: The Challenge for the 1990s by C. Colclough and K. Lewin - 1v, 1990-01-01 - ?; 01254163
  - Universities and Scientific Research Capacity in Africa and Asia by T. O. Eisemon, C. H. Davis - 1v, 1989-12-01 - ?; 01254167
  - Making Vocational Training Effective by J. Middleton, A. Ziderman, and A. Adams - 1v, 1990-03-01 - ?; 01255438
  - Teaching Quality and Student Achievement in Africa: The Case of Nigeria and Swaziland by Marlaine E. Lockheed and Andre Komenan - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255434
  - Family Effects on Students Achievement in Thailand and Malawi by Marlaine E. Lockheed, B. Fuller, and R. Nyirongo - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255436
  - The Determinants of Early Age Human Capital Formation: Evidence from Brazil by G. Psacharopoulos and A. M. Arriagada - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255442
  - Vocational Secondary Schools can be more Cost-effective than Academic Schools: the Case of Israel by S. Neuman and A. Ziderman - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255440
  - The Transition from School to the University under Restricted Entry: A Greek Tracer Study by G. Papas and G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1987-01-01 - ?; 01255446
  - Why Educational Reforms Fail: A Comparative Analysis by G. Psacharopoulos - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255447
  - Contingency Planning for Innovative Projects: Designing Education Reforms in Developing Countries by D. A. Rondinelli, J. Middleton and A. M. Verspoor - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255448
  - Education Development: Priorities for the Nineties by A. Verspoor - 1v, 1990-03-01 - ?; 01255450
  - Education Policy and Schooling Attainment in Malaysia and the Philippines by E. M. King and L. A. Lillard - 1v, 1987-01-01 - ?; 01255458
  - Training Alternatives for Youth: Results from Longitudinal Data by A. Ziderman - 1v, 1989-05-01 - ?; 01255453
  - Financing Training in Developing Countries: The Role of Payroll Taxes by J. Whalley and A. Ziderman - 1v, 1990-01-01 - ?; 01255464
  - Enhancing Girls' Learning Through Single-Sex Education: Evidence and a Policy Conundrum by E. Jimenez and M. E. Lockheed - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255473
  - The Relative Efficiency of Private and Public Schools in Developing Countries by E. Jimenez, M. E. Lockheed and V. Paqueo - 1v, 1990-01-03 - ?; 01255478
  - School Effects and Costs for Private and Public Schools in the Dominican Republic by E. Jimenez, M. E. Lockheed and V. Paqueo - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255480
  - Does Education Pay in the Labor Market? The Labor Force Participation, Occupation, and Earnings of Peruvian Women by E. M. King - 1v, 1989-01-01 - ?; 01255571
  - Annual Review of Education Lending: FY84 - 1v, 1984-08-30 - ?; 01255577
  - Education Policy and Schooling in Peru by E. M. King and R. T. Bellew - 1v, 1988-01-01 - ?; 01255572
  - The Center for Applied Linguistics: The Sudan: A Profile of Languages and their Use - 1v, 1975-01-01 - ?; 01255575
  - The Center for Applied Linguistics: Peru: A Profile of Languages and their Use - 1v, 1975-01-01 - ?; 01255576
  - Education Department - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01255578
  - Sector Lending for Education - 1v, 1981-03-09 - ?; 01255579
  - Guide for the Classification of Occupations by Skill Level by I. L. Hernstadt and M. Zymelman - 1v, 1980-01-01 - ?; 01255592
  - La Education al Servicio del Desarrollo Nacional: La Accio'n del Banco Mundial by A. Habte and S. Heyneman - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01255594
  - Educational Differences in Mortality of Children by S. H. Cochrane - 1v, 1980-04-01 - ?; 01255595
  - Socioeconomic and Demographic Aspects of School Enrollment and Attendance in Rural Botswana by D. Chernichovsky - 1v, 1985-01-01 - ?; 01255596
  - Influences on Academic Achievement: A Comparison of Results from Uganda and more Industrialized Societies; A Brief note on the Relationship between Socioeconomic Status and Test Performance among Ugandan Primary School Children by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1976-01-01 - ?; 01255597
  - Student Learning in Uganda: Textbook Availability and other Factors by S. P. Heyneman and D. T. Jamison - 1v, 1980-06-01 - ?; 01255598
  - Investment in Indian Education: Un-Economic? by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1980-01-01 - ?; 01255599
  - Instructions in the Mother Tongue: The Question of Logistics by S. Heyneman - 1v, 1978-01-01 - ?; 01255601
  - Why Impoverised Children do Well in Ugandan Schools by S.P. Heyneman - 1v, 1979-06-01 - ?; 01255602
  - Relationships between the Primary School Community and Academic Achievement in Uganda by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1977-01-01 - ?; 01255603
  - Investing in Education: A Quarter Century of World Bank Experience by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1985-01-01 - ?; 01255604
  - Diversifying Secondary School Curricula in Developing Countries: An Implementation History and some Policy Options by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1985-01-01 - ?; 01255605
  - Providing Full Primary Education in Small Schools - Alternative Arrangements - Institute of International Education - University of Stockholm, Sweden - Sixten Marklund, 1982-01-01 - ?; 01255751
  - The Nature of a Practical Curriculum by S. Heyneman - 1v, 1985-11-01 - ?; 01255606
  - The Effect of Primary School Quality on Academic Achievement across Twenty-nine High and Low Income Countries by S. P. Heyneman and W. A. Loxley - 1v, 1983-05-01 - ?; 01255607
  - Improving the Quality of Education by S. P. Heyneman - 1v, 1983-01-01 - ?; 01255608
  - Review of Education Lending, Actual (FY1974-78) and Projected (FY1979-83) by W. D. Haddad - 1v, 1980-08-01 - ?; 01255609
  - The World Bank's Education Sector Policy Paper: A Summary by W. D. Haddad - 1v, 1981-01-01 - ?; 01255610
  - The Two Elements of School Mapping: School Place Location Planning and School Resource Location Planning by S. P. Heyneman and W. Gould - 1v, 1978-09-01 - ?; 01255611